words,tags
RENTAL,O
AGREEMENT,O
THIS,O
DEED,O
OF,O
RENTAL,O
AGREEMENT,O
executed,O
at,O
Chennai,U-LOC
this,O
19th,O
day,O
of,O
August,O
2013,O
between,O
:,O
Mrs.,O
M.,B-PER
Geetha,L-PER
',',O
W,O
/,O
o,O
.,O
V.,B-PER
Manoharan,L-PER
',',O
aged,O
about,O
53,O
years,O
',',O
residing,O
at,O
No.62-D,O
',',O
Saravana,B-LOC
Flats,L-LOC
',',O
1st,B-LOC
Floor,L-LOC
',',O
Pinagapani,B-LOC
Street,L-LOC
',',O
Devaki,B-LOC
Nagar,L-LOC
',',O
Kundrathur,U-LOC
',',O
Chennai-600,U-LOC
069,O
.,O
Hereinafter,O
called,O
the,O
owner,O
(,O
Which,O
expression,O
shall,O
',',O
wherever,O
the,O
context,O
so,O
requires,O
',',O
be,O
deemed,O
to,O
mean,O
and,O
include,O
her,O
legal,O
heirs,O
',',O
executors,O
',',O
administrators,O
and,O
assignees,O
),O
of,O
the,O
one,O
part,O
.,O
AND,O
To,O
and,O
in,O
favour,O
of,O
M,O
/,O
s,O
.,O
Siruvani,B-ORG
Traders,I-ORG
Private,I-ORG
Limited,L-ORG
Represented,O
by,O
Mr.,O
J.,B-PER
L.,I-PER
Saravana,L-PER
',',O
aged,O
about,O
33,O
years,O
S,O
/,O
o,O
M,O
S,B-LOC
Jambulingam,L-LOC
',',O
residing,O
at,O
No,O
.,O
13/5,O
',',O
Janakiraman,B-LOC
Street,L-LOC
',',O
Muthurangam,B-LOC
Block,L-LOC
',',O
Jafferkhanpet,U-LOC
',',O
Ashok,B-LOC
Nagar,L-LOC
',',O
Chennai,U-LOC
-,O
600,O
083,O
',',O
hereinafter,O
called,O
the,O
tenant,O
(,O
which,O
expression,O
shall,O
',',O
wherever,O
the,O
context,O
so,O
requires,O
be,O
deemed,O
to,O
mean,O
and,O
include,O
his,O
successors-,O
in-,O
interest,O
and,O
assignees,O
),O
of,O
the,O
other,O
part,O
witnesses,O
as,O
follows,O
:,O
-2-,O
Whereas,O
Mrs.,O
M.,B-PER
Geetha,L-PER
is,O
the,O
absolute,O
owner,O
of,O
the,O
property,O
at,O
No.62-D,O
',',O
Saravana,B-LOC
Flats,L-LOC
',',O
1st,B-LOC
Floor,L-LOC
',',O
Pinagapani,B-LOC
Street,L-LOC
',',O
Devaki,B-LOC
Nagar,L-LOC
',',O
Kundrathur,U-LOC
',',O
Chennai,U-LOC
-,O
600,O
069,O
measuring,O
250,O
sq.ft,O
and,O
in,O
possession,O
and,O
enjoyment,O
of,O
the,O
same,O
.,O
Whereas,O
the,O
tenant,O
has,O
approached,O
the,O
owner,O
to,O
take,O
on,O
rent,O
the,O
First,B-ORG
Floor,L-ORG
premises,O
of,O
the,O
building,O
referred,O
in,O
the,O
schedule,O
hereunder,O
for,O
running,O
their,O
business,O
activities,O
and,O
the,O
owner,O
has,O
also,O
agreed,O
for,O
the,O
same,O
.,O
WHEREAS,O
the,O
parties,O
herein,O
mentioned,O
felt,O
expedient,O
to,O
reduce,O
the,O
terms,O
and,O
conditions,O
of,O
the,O
rental,O
agreement,O
into,O
writing,O
.,O
THIS,O
RENTAL,O
AGREEMENT,O
WITNESSETH,O
AS,O
FOLLOWS,O
:,O
That,O
in,O
pursuance,O
of,O
the,O
above,O
said,O
offer,O
and,O
acceptance,O
and,O
in,O
consideration,O
of,O
a,O
monthly,O
rent,O
of,O
Rs.2500,O
/-,O
herein,O
mentioned,O
',',O
the,O
owner,O
hereby,O
lets,O
out,O
the,O
First,B-ORG
Floor,L-ORG
of,O
the,O
building,O
bearing,O
',',O
No.62-D,O
',',O
Saravana,B-LOC
Flats,L-LOC
',',O
1st,B-LOC
Floor,L-LOC
',',O
Pinagapani,B-LOC
Street,L-LOC
',',O
Devaki,B-LOC
Nagar,L-LOC
',',O
Kundrathur,U-LOC
',',O
Chennai-600,U-LOC
069,O
subject,O
to,O
the,O
terms,O
',',O
conditions,O
and,O
convenants,O
specified,O
hereunder,O
.,O
This,O
Rental,B-MISC
Agreement,L-MISC
shall,O
be,O
for,O
a,O
period,O
of,O
11,O
Months,O
commencing,O
from,O
August,O
2014,O
.,O
The,O
agreed,O
rent,O
of,O
Rs.2500/-,O
has,O
to,O
be,O
paid,O
on,O
or,O
before,O
5th,O
of,O
every,O
month,O
.,O
While,O
the,O
owner,O
shall,O
bear,O
the,O
property,O
tax,O
',',O
water,O
tax,O
',',O
in,O
respect,O
of,O
the,O
Rented,B-MISC
Flat,L-MISC
',',O
the,O
tenant,O
shall,O
bear,O
Electricity,B-ORG
',',I-ORG
Maintenance,I-ORG
and,I-ORG
Water,I-ORG
Charges,L-ORG
.,O
The,O
tenant,O
shall,O
use,O
the,O
schedule,O
property,O
only,O
for,O
the,O
Office,U-ORG
use,O
.,O
The,O
tenant,O
hereby,O
covenants,O
with,O
the,O
owner,O
and,O
assures,O
here,O
that,O
.,O
They,O
will,O
keep,O
the,O
flat,O
in,O
a,O
neat,O
and,O
tenantable,O
condition,O
.,O
They,O
will,O
not,O
carry,O
out,O
any,O
structural,O
alternation,O
to,O
the,O
flat,O
leased,O
out,O
;,O
They,O
will,O
not,O
cause,O
any,O
nuisance,O
either,O
to,O
the,O
owner,O
or,O
to,O
the,O
other,O
occupants,O
in,O
the,O
building,O
/,O
neighbors,O
.,O
On,O
the,O
expiry,O
of,O
the,O
lease,O
he,O
will,O
peacefully,O
surrender,O
vacant,O
possession,O
of,O
the,O
schedule,O
property,O
to,O
the,O
owner,O
.,O
The,O
tenant,O
shall,O
not,O
sub,O
-,O
lease,O
/,O
Sub,O
-,O
let,O
the,O
flat,O
leased,O
out,O
to,O
them,O
to,O
anyone,O
Notwithstanding,O
anything,O
contained,O
herein,O
either,O
party,O
can,O
terminate,O
this,O
lease,O
by,O
serving,O
the,O
other,O
party,O
a,O
notice,O
in,O
writing,O
4,O
months,O
in,O
advance,O
.,O
The,O
tenant,O
shall,O
permit,O
the,O
owner,O
or,O
her,O
agents,O
to,O
inspect,O
the,O
flat,O
leased,O
out,O
at,O
all,O
reasonable,O
time,O
to,O
see,O
whether,O
all,O
the,O
terms,O
and,O
conditions,O
of,O
the,O
lease,O
are,O
complied,O
with,O
by,O
the,O
tenant,O
.,O
The,O
rental,O
agreement,O
can,O
be,O
renewed,O
once,O
in,O
every,O
11,O
months,O
with,O
the,O
mutual,O
consent,O
of,O
the,O
parties,O
to,O
this,O
agreement,O
IN,O
WITNESS,O
WHEREOF,O
THE,O
PARHES,O
HERETO,U-PER
HAVE,O
SET,O
AND,O
SUBSCRIBED,O
THEIR,O
RESPECTIVE,O
HANDS,O
AND,O
SEALS,O
HEREUNTO,O
ON,O
THE,O
DAY,O
AND,O
YEAR,O
FIRST,O
ABOVE,O
WRISTTEN,O
WITNESSES,O
:,O
1,O
.,O
(,O
OWNER,O
),O
2,O
.,O
(,O
TENANT,O
),O
