words,tags
INDIA,U-LOC
NON,O
JUDICIAL,O
Government,O
of,O
Karnataka,U-LOC
e,O
-,O
Stamp,O
IN,O
-,O
KA54376245967338,O
M,O
21-Apr-2014,O
10:50,O
AM,O
NONACC,O
(,O
BK)/,U-PER
kakscub08/,O
TUMKUR/,O
KA,O
-,O
TU,B-PER
SUB,L-PER
IN,O
-,O
KAKAKSCUB0864505677712874,O
M,O
S,O
T,O
NAGAVENI,O
WO,O
H,O
V,O
NARAYANA,O
Article,O
12,O
Bond,O
AGREEMENT,O
0,O
(,O
Zero,O
),O
S,O
T,O
NAGAVENI,O
WO,O
H,O
V,O
NARAYANA,U-LOC
H,O
N,B-LOC
MADHU,L-LOC
S,O
O,O
H,O
V,O
NARAYANA,U-LOC
S,O
T,O
NAGAVENI,O
WO,O
H,O
V,O
NARAYANA,U-LOC
200,O
(,O
Two,B-MISC
Hundred,L-MISC
only,O
),O
Please,O
write,O
or,O
type,O
below,O
this,O
line,O
.,O
Rental,O
Agreement,O
Rental,O
agreement,O
was,O
executed,O
on,O
Two,O
thousand,O
fourteen,O
April,O
twenty,O
first,O
(,O
21/04/14,O
),O
',',O
Between,O
S,O
T,B-ORG
Nagaveni,L-ORG
(,O
owner,O
),O
C,O
/,O
o,O
Narayan,U-LOC
H,O
V,O
Resident,O
of,O
Vanasuma,U-LOC
nilaya,O
Tumkur,O
District,O
SS,O
puram,O
',',O
8th,B-LOC
Cross,L-LOC
',',O
7th,B-LOC
Main,L-LOC
and,O
Mr,O
Madhu,B-LOC
H,I-LOC
N,L-LOC
residing,O
at,O
8th,O
cross,O
7th,O
main,O
Sspuram,B-LOC
Tumkur,L-LOC
.,O
NOW,O
THIS,O
TENANCY,O
AGREEMENT,O
WITNESSETH,O
AS,O
FOLLOWS,O
:,O
Purpose,O
of,O
use,O
Rental,O
for,O
flour,O
mill,O
and,O
Dairy,O
products,O
The,O
TENANT,U-ORG
has,O
paid,O
this,O
day,O
a,O
sum,O
of,O
Rs,U-MISC
.,O
'50,000',O
(,O
Rupees,O
fifty,O
thousand,O
only,O
),O
',',O
being,O
advance,O
',',O
by,O
cash,O
on,O
which,O
is,O
the,O
receipt,O
of,O
the,O
same,O
is,O
herewith,O
acknowledged,O
by,O
the,O
owner,O
.,O
The,O
Tenant,O
shall,O
pay,O
a,O
monthly,O
rent,O
of,O
Rs,O
'5,000/-(Rupees',O
sixteen,O
thousand,O
only,O
),O
on,O
or,O
before,O
5th,O
of,O
every,O
English,U-MISC
calendar,O
month,O
.,O
The,O
term,O
of,O
this,O
agreement,O
of,O
rent,O
commenced,O
from,O
<,O
21/04/2014,O
>,O
This,O
agreement,O
will,O
remain,O
in,O
force,O
a,O
period,O
of,O
05,O
months,O
.,O
During,O
the,O
term,O
the,O
Security,O
deposit,O
amount,O
will,O
not,O
carry,O
any,O
interest,O
and,O
this,O
amount,O
fully,O
refundable,O
to,O
TENANT,U-ORG
by,O
OWNER,U-ORG
while,O
termination,O
of,O
this,O
agreement,O
or,O
rent,O
after,O
deducting,O
arrears,O
of,O
dues,O
of,O
TENANT,U-ORG
such,O
as,O
electricity,O
Bill,U-MISC
',',O
damages,O
',',O
rent,O
etc,O
.,O
',',O
thereon,O
',',O
to,O
which,O
both,O
the,O
parties,O
in,O
due,O
course,O
of,O
the,O
term,O
TENANT,U-ORG
shall,O
pay,O
thereon,O
to,O
the,O
concerned,O
authority,O
as,O
and,O
when,O
it,O
falls,O
due,O
.,O
In,O
addition,O
to,O
that,O
TENANT,U-PER
himself,O
incurred,O
normal,O
wear,O
and,O
tear,O
maintenance,O
charges,O
out,O
of,O
his,O
own,O
cost,O
and,O
risk,O
.,O
10,O
.,O
The,O
TENANT,U-ORG
shall,O
pay,O
to,O
the,O
owner,O
an,O
enchanced,O
rent,O
of,O
Rs,U-MISC
5,O
%,O
of,O
monthly,O
rent,O
',',O
for,O
every,O
year,O
over,O
and,O
above,O
the,O
then,O
existing,O
rental,O
at,O
the,O
end,O
of,O
the,O
lease,O
period,O
',',O
if,O
the,O
lease,O
were,O
to,O
be,O
continued,O
by,O
fresh,O
deed,O
for,O
over,O
12,O
months,O
.,O
SCHEDULE,O
Details,O
The,O
premises,O
bearing,O
Tumkur,B-LOC
Taluk,L-LOC
',',O
Gukur,B-LOC
Hobli,L-LOC
',',O
Naruganahalli,U-LOC
post,O
',',O
Honnenhalli,B-LOC
Village,L-LOC
Survey,O
Number,O
10/03,O
and,O
10/04/,O
having,O
1.13,O
Acers,U-MISC
is,O
used,O
for,O
industries,O
land,O
having,O
40x30,O
Shed,O
and,O
watch,O
men,O
room,O
East,O
:,O
other,O
properties,O
',',O
West,O
:,O
road,O
',',O
North,B-LOC
Hanumantha,L-LOC
rayyappa,O
Land,U-LOC
',',O
South,U-LOC
:,O
Chinnama,B-ORG
Land,L-ORG
owner,O
.,O
WITNESSES,O
OWNER,B-ORG
TENANT,L-ORG
