words,tags
This,O
agreement,O
is,O
made,O
on,O
the,O
1st,O
day,O
of,O
May,O
2016,O
(,O
01.05.2016,O
),O
between,O
ANAND,B-ORG
RAJ,L-ORG
',',O
S,U-LOC
/,O
o,O
.,O
CJ,B-PER
Scaria,L-PER
',',O
aged,O
26,O
years,O
',',O
residing,O
at,O
Changankariyil,B-LOC
House,I-LOC
Karuvanchal,I-LOC
PO,L-LOC
',',O
Alakode,U-LOC
',',O
Taliparamba,U-LOC
',',O
Kannur,B-LOC
Pincode,L-LOC
:,O
670571,O
(,O
hereinafter,O
referred,O
to,O
as,O
the,O
LESSEE,U-MISC
),O
on,O
the,O
One,O
part,O
AND,O
BEENA,B-ORG
PURATHAYIL,I-ORG
MADHAVAN,L-ORG
W,O
/,O
O,O
Parapattil,B-PER
Puthra,I-PER
Valsalan,L-PER
aged,O
62,O
years,O
',',O
residing,O
at,O
XXII/688,U-PER
',',O
Nandavanam,U-LOC
',',O
Chcmbumukku,U-LOC
',',O
Thrikkakara,B-LOC
P,I-LOC
O.,I-LOC
Cochin,L-LOC
682021,O
.,O
(,O
hereinafter,O
referred,O
to,O
as,O
the,O
LESSOR,U-MISC
),O
on,O
the,O
Other,O
part,O
.,O
BEENA,B-ORG
PURATHAYIL,I-ORG
MADHAVAN,L-ORG
LESSOR,O
-2-,O
Where,O
as,O
the,O
Lessor,U-MISC
is,O
the,O
absolute,O
owner,O
in,O
possession,O
of,O
the,O
Flat,B-MISC
No,I-MISC
.,I-MISC
3E,L-MISC
',',O
Regal,B-LOC
Valancia,L-LOC
',',O
Thrikkakara-,U-MISC
682021,O
(,O
Semi,B-LOC
Furnished,L-LOC
flat,O
with,O
Items,O
5,O
Fan,O
',',O
Kitchen,O
and,O
bedroom,O
Cabinets,O
',',O
Light,O
fixtures,O
),O
situated,O
within,O
the,O
limit,O
of,O
Thrikkakara,B-ORG
Municipality,L-ORG
and,O
whereas,O
the,O
Lessee,U-MISC
has,O
requested,O
the,O
Lessor,U-MISC
to,O
let,O
the,O
said,O
Flat,O
for,O
residential,O
use,O
of,O
the,O
Lessee,U-LOC
and,O
the,O
Lessor,U-MISC
has,O
accepted,O
the,O
same,O
.,O
BEENA,B-ORG
PURATHAYIL,I-ORG
MADHAVAN,L-ORG
LESSOR,O
NOW,O
THIS,O
DEED,O
WITNESSES,O
AS,O
FOLLOWS:-,O
The,O
Lessee,U-MISC
shall,O
pay,O
the,O
Lessor,U-MISC
a,O
monthly,O
rent,O
of,O
Rs,O
.,O
11500/-,O
(,O
Eleven,O
Thousand,B-MISC
Five,I-MISC
Hundred,I-MISC
Only,L-MISC
),O
regularly,O
and,O
punctually,O
without,O
any,O
delay,O
or,O
default,O
on,O
or,O
before,O
5th,O
day,O
of,O
every,O
month,O
in,O
the,O
English,B-MISC
Calendar,L-MISC
and,O
the,O
receipt,O
of,O
the,O
same,O
to,O
be,O
obtained,O
.,O
The,O
Lessee,U-ORG
shall,O
pay,O
a,O
sum,O
of,O
Rs,U-MISC
.,O
35000/-,O
(,O
Rupees,O
Thirty,O
-,O
Five,B-MISC
Thousand,L-MISC
only,O
),O
as,O
security,O
deposit,O
to,O
the,O
Lessor,U-ORG
free,O
of,O
interest,O
and,O
which,O
shall,O
be,O
refunded,O
at,O
the,O
time,O
of,O
expiry,O
of,O
the,O
lease,O
period,O
after,O
deducting,O
dues,O
',',O
loss,O
and,O
damages,O
',',O
if,O
any,O
.,O
At,O
all,O
times,O
during,O
the,O
term,O
of,O
lease,O
the,O
Lessee,U-ORG
shall,O
keep,O
and,O
maintain,O
the,O
said,O
flat,O
with,O
all,O
its,O
fitting,O
',',O
and,O
fixtures,O
in,O
proper,O
clean,O
and,O
neat,O
conditions,O
.,O
The,O
Lessee,U-MISC
shall,O
use,O
the,O
flat,O
for,O
residential,O
purpose,O
only,O
.,O
The,O
Lessee,U-MISC
shall,O
not,O
make,O
any,O
alteration,O
or,O
modifications,O
in,O
the,O
said,O
flat,O
.,O
The,O
Lessee,U-MISC
shall,O
not,O
use,O
the,O
flat,O
so,O
as,O
to,O
destroy,O
or,O
reduce,O
its,O
value,O
or,O
utility,O
in,O
any,O
manner,O
.,O
The,O
Lessee,U-ORG
shall,O
not,O
transfer,O
his,O
right,O
or,O
sublet,O
the,O
said,O
flat,O
or,O
any,O
part,O
there,O
of,O
to,O
anybody,O
.,O
The,O
period,O
of,O
lease,O
shall,O
be,O
11,O
months,O
from,O
01,O
-,O
05,O
-,O
2016,O
on,O
the,O
expiry,O
of,O
the,O
above,O
period,O
Lessee,U-MISC
shall,O
vacate,O
and,O
deliver,O
the,O
possession,O
of,O
the,O
flat,O
to,O
the,O
Lessor,U-ORG
in,O
good,O
conditions,O
as,O
it,O
is,O
on,O
this,O
day,O
.,O
BEENA,B-ORG
PURATHAY1L,I-ORG
MADHAVAN,L-ORG
LESSOR,O
The,O
Electricity,B-ORG
and,I-ORG
Water,L-ORG
charges,O
and,O
any,O
other,O
charges,O
connected,O
with,O
self,O
usage,O
of,O
the,O
flat,O
to,O
be,O
paid,O
by,O
the,O
Lessee,U-ORG
in,O
addition,O
to,O
the,O
rent,O
',',O
Lessee,U-ORG
also,O
liable,O
to,O
pay,O
a,O
maintenance,O
Charges,O
to,O
the,O
Flat,B-ORG
Owners,I-ORG
Association,L-ORG
and,O
obtain,O
receipt,O
for,O
the,O
same,O
.,O
Explosive,O
items,O
not,O
to,O
be,O
kept,O
inside,O
the,O
flat,O
.,O
That,O
both,O
parties,O
are,O
at,O
liberty,O
to,O
evict,O
or,O
vacate,O
the,O
flat,O
before,O
the,O
expiry,O
of,O
the,O
period,O
of,O
tenancy,O
by,O
giving,O
one,O
month,O
prior,O
registered,O
notice,O
.,O
The,O
period,O
of,O
agreement,O
shall,O
be,O
renewed,O
for,O
further,O
period,O
if,O
mutually,O
agreed,O
between,O
both,O
parties,O
on,O
or,O
before,O
expiry,O
of,O
this,O
agreement\,O
The,O
lessee,O
shall,O
be,O
liable,O
to,O
pay,O
all,O
costs,O
/replacements,O
for,O
all,O
such,O
items,O
that,O
are,O
part,O
of,O
flat,O
/,O
furnishings,O
in,O
the,O
instance,O
of,O
damages,O
caused,O
or,O
resulted,O
from,O
misuse,O
/,O
purposeful,O
acts,O
from,O
the,O
side,O
of,O
lessee,O
/or,O
shall,O
be,O
recovered,O
from,O
the,O
paid,O
advance,O
if,O
limited,O
within,O
the,O
same,O
.,O
14,O
Lesse,U-MISC
shall,O
have,O
the,O
right,O
to,O
use,O
one,O
car,O
porch,O
that,O
belongs,O
to,O
the,O
flat,O
Valancy,B-ORG
3E,L-ORG
In,O
witness,O
whereof,O
the,O
parties,O
here,O
to,O
have,O
signed,O
this,O
deed,O
on,O
the,O
day,O
month,O
and,O
year,O
first,O
above,O
written,O
.,O
BEENA,B-ORG
PURATHAYIL,I-ORG
MADHAVAN,L-ORG
LESSOR,O
Witness,O
1,O
.,O
2,O
.,O
This,O
Document,O
is,O
Type,O
Written,O
.,O
Corrections,B-ORG
Nill,L-ORG
.,O
