words,tags
RENTfft,O
ENT,O
This,O
Rental,O
Agreement,O
is,O
made,O
and,O
executed,O
on,O
this,O
the,O
.,O
?,O
.,O
?,O
?,O
&,O
day,O
of,O
2010,O
at,O
Hyderabad,U-LOC
',',O
by,O
and,O
between,O
:,O
M.,U-PER
V,O
',',O
V,O
«,O
VI,O
JAY,U-PER
A,O
SHANKAR,U-PER
',',O
S,O
/,O
o,O
',',O
M,O
',',O
Rangaiah,U-PER
R,O
/,O
o,O
.,O
Flat,O
No,O
.,O
309,O
',',O
SHEETAL.ENCLAVE,U-PER
',',O
JE12DIJNETLA,U-PER
',',O
Ranga,B-PER
Reddy,I-PER
Districto,L-PER
(,O
Hereinafter,U-LOC
called,O
the,O
“,O
LANDLORD,O
”,O
),O
AND,O
MADDIREDDY,O
BHARGAVA,O
REDDY,O
',',O
S,O
/,O
O,O
',',O
MADDIREDDY,O
SUBBA,O
REDDY,O
',',O
R,O
/,O
o,O
',',O
Flat,O
No.303,O
',',O
SHEETAL,B-LOC
ENCLAVE,L-LOC
',',O
JEEDIMETLA,O
',',O
Ranga,B-LOC
Reddy,I-LOC
District,L-LOC
•,O
(,O
Hereinafter,O
called,O
the,O
“,O
TENANT,O
”,O
),O
WHEREAS,O
the,O
Landlord,O
is,O
the,O
absolute,O
owner,O
and,O
possessor,O
of,O
the,O
bearing,O
No,B-MISC
Flat,I-MISC
NOe2sfi,L-MISC
303,O
»,O
sheetal,O
enclave,O
',',O
jeedimetla,O
RANGA,B-ORG
REDDY,I-ORG
DISTRICT,I-ORG
WHEREAS,L-ORG
the,O
tenant,O
approached,O
the,O
landlord,O
and,O
requested,O
him,O
/,O
her,O
to,O
let,O
-,O
out,O
the,O
said,O
House,B-ORG
/,I-ORG
Plot,L-ORG
on,O
the,O
rental,O
basis,O
and,O
the,O
same,O
is,O
accepted,O
.,O
WHEREAS,O
the,O
tenant,O
agreed,O
to,O
pay,O
the,O
monthly,O
rent,O
on,O
or,O
before,O
5th,O
day,O
of,O
every,O
month,O
at,O
Rs,O
9.99.7.9,O
°,O
p.m.,O
and,O
agreed,O
to,O
bear,O
Electricity,O
',',O
Water,B-MISC
Charges,L-MISC
etc,O
.,O
',',O
as,O
applicable,O
',',O
is,O
valid,O
from,O
11,O
'months,.for',O
the,O
purposes,O
of,O
.Resident,O
iai__|iroofo,O
In,O
witnesses,O
whereof,O
both,O
the,O
parties,O
have,O
signed,O
on,O
this,O
the,O
Rental,B-MISC
Agreement,L-MISC
before,O
the,O
following,O
witnesses,O
:,O
WITNESSES,O
:,O
