words,tags
RENTAL,O
AGREEMENT,O
This,O
Rental,O
Agreement,O
made,O
and,O
executed,O
at,O
Bangalore,U-LOC
on,O
this,O
1st,O
day,O
April,O
two,O
thousand,O
eleven,O
(,O
01/04/2011,O
),O
',',O
between,O
Prof.,O
K.,B-PER
Parthasarathy,L-PER
',',O
S,U-LOC
/,O
o,O
.,O
Late,O
T.S.Krishna,B-PER
Iyengar,L-PER
aged,O
about,O
75,O
years,O
',',O
No,O
.,O
46,O
',',O
Srinivasa,U-PER
',',O
2nd,O
Main,B-LOC
Road,L-LOC
',',O
Hanumanthanagar,U-PER
',',O
Bangalore-560019,U-LOC
',',O
herein,O
after,O
called,O
“,O
LESSOR,U-PER
”,O
(,O
which,O
expression,O
shall,O
where,O
-,O
ever,O
the,O
context,O
so,O
requires,O
or,O
permits,O
mean,O
and,O
include,O
here,O
heirs,O
',',O
executors,O
',',O
administrators,O
and,O
assign,O
),O
of,O
the,O
FIRST,O
PART,O
.,O
AND,O
Mr.,O
Veerabrahmam,B-PER
Bathini,L-PER
',',O
S,O
/,O
o,O
Mr,O
.,O
Lingaiah,B-PER
Bathini,L-PER
aged,O
about,O
28,O
years,O
(,O
Sr,O
.,O
Engineer,O
-,O
PSS,U-PER
working,O
at,O
Power,B-ORG
Research,I-ORG
and,I-ORG
Development,I-ORG
Consultants,L-ORG
',',O
#,B-MISC
5,L-MISC
',',O
11th,O
cross,O
',',O
2nd,O
stage,O
',',O
West,O
of,O
Chord,B-LOC
Road,L-LOC
',',O
Bangalore-560086,U-LOC
',',O
herein,O
after,O
called,O
“,O
LESSEE,O
”,O
(,O
Tenant,O
),O
of,O
the,O
SECOND,O
PART,O
.,O
WITNESSETH,O
AS,O
FOLLOWS,O
:,O
The,O
Lessor,O
hereby,O
covenants,O
with,O
Lessee,U-PER
and,O
warrants,O
that,O
he,O
is,O
the,O
owner,O
and,O
as,O
such,O
as,O
the,O
right,O
and,O
the,O
authority,O
to,O
lease,O
the,O
First,B-ORG
Floor,L-ORG
of,O
premises,O
No,O
.,O
146,O
',',O
Krishna,B-PER
Krupa,L-PER
',',O
3rd,B-LOC
Cross,L-LOC
',',O
1st,B-LOC
Main,L-LOC
',',O
VHBCSL,B-LOC
Layout,L-LOC
',',O
West,U-LOC
of,O
Chord,B-LOC
Road,L-LOC
',',O
Bangalore-560086,U-LOC
.,O
The,O
Lessor,U-MISC
hereby,O
agrees,O
to,O
let,O
to,O
the,O
Lessee,U-LOC
the,O
First,B-LOC
Floor,L-LOC
of,O
the,O
premises,O
',',O
No,O
.,O
146,O
',',O
Krishna,B-PER
Krupa,L-PER
',',O
3rd,B-LOC
Cross,L-LOC
',',O
1st,B-LOC
Main,L-LOC
',',O
VHBCSL,B-LOC
Layout,L-LOC
',',O
West,U-LOC
of,O
Chord,B-LOC
Road,L-LOC
',',O
Bangalore-,U-LOC
560086,O
on,O
the,O
following,O
terms,O
conditions,O
.,O
The,O
Lessee,U-ORG
will,O
pay,O
the,O
Lessor,U-MISC
for,O
the,O
premises,O
herein,O
described,O
in,O
the,O
schedule,O
',',O
a,O
monthly,O
rent,O
of,O
'Rs.8,000/-',O
(,O
Ruppes,O
eight,O
thousand,O
only,O
),O
.,O
The,O
rent,O
shall,O
be,O
paid,O
on,O
or,O
before,O
10th,O
of,O
each,O
calendar,O
month,O
without,O
deductions,O
whatsoever,O
.,O
If,O
the,O
Lessee,U-ORG
fails,O
to,O
pay,O
the,O
monthly,O
rent,O
in,O
time,O
',',O
the,O
Lessor,U-ORG
shall,O
have,O
the,O
liberty,O
to,O
resume,O
the,O
schedule,O
premises,O
without,O
re,O
-,O
course,O
to,O
any,O
action,O
',',O
legal,O
or,O
other,O
wise,O
.,O
The,O
Lessee,U-ORG
shall,O
not,O
pay,O
any,O
advance,O
to,O
the,O
premises,O
.,O
This,O
rental,O
agreement,O
shall,O
be,O
valid,O
for,O
a,O
period,O
of,O
twelve,O
months,O
',',O
from,O
the,O
date,O
of,O
execution,O
and,O
subject,O
to,O
renewal,O
on,O
expiry,O
of,O
the,O
above,O
lease,O
period,O
on,O
execution,O
of,O
fresh,O
LEASE,O
-,O
DEED,U-ORG
on,O
mutual,O
consent,O
.,O
Under,O
no,O
circumstances,O
',',O
the,O
schedule,O
premises,O
shall,O
be,O
sublet,O
or,O
underlet,O
to,O
any,O
one,O
else,O
but,O
shall,O
be,O
used,O
by,O
lessee,O
for,O
his,O
bonafide,O
residence,O
only,O
.,O
The,O
Lessee,U-ORG
undertakes,O
the,O
full,O
responsibility,O
for,O
the,O
payment,O
of,O
all,O
electric,O
and,O
water,O
charges,O
and,O
receipts,O
retained,O
for,O
record,O
.,O
Additions,O
or,O
alterations,O
shall,O
not,O
be,O
made,O
to,O
th,O
existing,O
structure,O
without,O
written,O
consent,O
from,O
the,O
Lessor,U-ORG
.,O
If,O
any,O
damage,O
is,O
caused,O
to,O
the,O
schedule,O
premises,O
',',O
the,O
same,O
shall,O
be,O
got,O
repaired,O
by,O
the,O
Lessee,U-MISC
at,O
his,O
own,O
cost,O
.,O
The,O
Lessee,U-ORG
upon,O
termination,O
of,O
this,O
agreement,O
will,O
peacefully,O
and,O
quietly,O
leave,O
to,O
the,O
Lessor,U-ORG
the,O
possession,O
of,O
the,O
said,O
premises,O
together,O
with,O
the,O
fixtures,O
and,O
fittings,O
as,O
given,O
below,O
in,O
substantially,O
same,O
condition,O
by,O
the,O
lessee,O
except,O
for,O
the,O
normal,O
wear,O
and,O
tear,O
.,O
The,O
Lessor,U-PER
or,O
his,O
authorized,O
agent,O
shall,O
be,O
permitted,O
to,O
enter,O
schedule,O
premises,O
at,O
all,O
reasonable,O
hours,O
to,O
inspect,O
the,O
same,O
for,O
its,O
wear,O
and,O
tear,O
.,O
Both,O
the,O
parties,O
agree,O
that,O
this,O
lease,O
agreement,O
may,O
be,O
terminated,O
by,O
the,O
Lessee,U-MISC
by,O
giving,O
three,O
months,O
notice,O
in,O
writing,O
.,O
SCHEDULE,O
The,O
first,O
floor,O
of,O
the,O
No,B-MISC
.,I-MISC
146,L-MISC
',',O
VHBCSL,B-LOC
Layout,L-LOC
',',O
3rd,O
cross,O
',',O
1st,B-LOC
Main,L-LOC
',',O
Bangalore-560086,U-LOC
bounded,O
by,O
East,B-LOC
by,L-LOC
147,O
and,O
North,U-LOC
by,O
161,O
West,O
by,O
Road,U-LOC
and,O
South,B-LOC
by,I-LOC
Road,L-LOC
