words,tags
RENTAL,O
AGREEMENT,O
This,O
RENTAL,O
AGREEMENT,O
is,O
made,O
&,O
executed,O
on,O
20,O
April,O
2011,O
between,O
:,O
Mrs,O
.,O
Asha,B-PER
Ramesh,L-PER
&,O
Mr,O
.,O
Ramesh,U-PER
.,O
K.N.,B-PER
Residing,L-PER
at,O
1st,B-LOC
Floor,L-LOC
',',O
82A,O
',',O
Vysya,B-LOC
Bank,I-LOC
Colony,L-LOC
',',O
ShantiniketanLayout,U-LOC
',',O
Arakere,B-LOC
Post,L-LOC
',',O
Bannerghatta,B-LOC
Road,L-LOC
',',O
Bangalore-560076,U-LOC
',',O
henceforth,O
calld,O
the,O
LESSOR,U-ORG
(,O
OWNERS,U-ORG
),O
',',O
which,O
term,O
include,O
their,O
heirs,O
',',O
administrators,O
and,O
assignees,O
of,O
the,O
ONE,B-ORG
PART,L-ORG
AND,O
Mrs,O
.,O
Sadasivuni,B-MISC
Deepti,I-MISC
&,I-MISC
Mr,L-MISC
.,O
Sadasivuni,B-LOC
Kiran,L-LOC
native,O
53,O
-,O
38,O
-,O
20,O
',',O
KRM,B-PER
Colony,L-PER
',',O
Maddilapalem,U-PER
',',O
Vishakapatnam,U-LOC
',',O
AP530013,O
henceforth,O
called,O
the,O
LESSEE,U-MISC
(,O
TENANT,U-MISC
),O
which,O
term,O
shall,O
mean,O
and,O
include,O
their,O
heirs,O
',',O
executors,O
',',O
administrators,O
',',O
legal,O
representatives,O
and,O
assigns,O
of,O
the,O
OTHER,O
PART,O
witnessed,O
as,O
follows,O
:,O
WHEREAS,O
the,O
LESSOR,U-MISC
at,O
the,O
request,O
of,O
the,O
LESSEE,U-MISC
agreed,O
to,O
let,O
out,O
the,O
entire,O
2nd,O
floor,O
premise,O
except,O
the,O
front,O
room,O
',',O
mentioned,O
in,O
the,O
schedule,O
below,O
on,O
a,O
monthly,O
rent,O
of,O
Rs.5500/-(Five,O
thousand,O
five,O
hundred,O
only,O
},O
The,O
LESSEE,U-MISC
shall,O
pay,O
the,O
monthly,O
rent,O
on,O
or,O
before,O
5th,O
of,O
every,O
English,U-MISC
calendarmonth,O
.,O
The,O
LESSEE,U-MISC
has,O
deposited,O
with,O
the,O
LESSOR,U-MISC
a,O
sum,O
of,O
Rs,O
.,O
'55,000/-(Rs',O
.,O
Fifty,O
five,O
thousand,O
only,O
),O
as,O
Non,B-ORG
Interest,I-ORG
Bearing,I-ORG
Security,I-ORG
Deposit,L-ORG
and,O
the,O
LESSOR,U-ORG
have,O
acknowledged,O
with,O
recept,O
.,O
The,O
LESSOR,U-ORG
will,O
return,O
the,O
deposit,O
to,O
the,O
LESSEES,U-MISC
on,O
the,O
termination,O
of,O
rent,O
agreement,O
less,O
dues,O
if,O
any,O
.,O
The,O
rent,O
agreement,O
shall,O
be,O
in,O
force,O
for,O
a,O
period,O
of,O
11,O
(,O
months,O
),O
from,O
the,O
date,O
of,O
Tenancy,O
.,O
The,O
LESSEE,U-MISC
shall,O
pay,O
the,O
monthly,O
electricity,O
charges,O
to,O
the,O
concerned,O
authorities,O
directly,O
and,O
keep,O
a,O
record,O
.,O
The,O
LESSEE,U-MISC
shall,O
pay,O
half,O
of,O
the,O
water,O
bill,O
&,B-ORG
Association,I-ORG
Bill,L-ORG
that,O
comes,O
on,O
a,O
monthly,O
basis,O
',',O
to,O
the,O
LESSOR,U-ORG
towards,O
water,O
&,O
sewerage,O
.,O
Motor,O
and,O
electricity,O
charges,O
will,O
be,O
Rs,U-MISC
.,O
100,O
/,O
month,O
extra,O
.,O
The,O
LESSEE,O
shall,O
maintain,O
the,O
cleanliness,O
of,O
the,O
premise,O
inside,O
and,O
outside,O
on,O
a,O
daily,O
basis,O
',',O
to,O
take,O
necessary,O
timely,O
action,O
and,O
maintain,O
the,O
premise,O
well,O
.,O
LESSOR,U-ORG
has,O
the,O
right,O
to,O
recover,O
appropriate,O
amount,O
if,O
there,O
is,O
loss,O
/,O
deterioration,O
.,O
It,O
is,O
hereby,O
agreed,O
that,O
2{Two,U-MISC
},O
months,O
'''',O
notice,O
is,O
required,O
on,O
either,O
side,O
for,O
the,O
termination,O
of,O
this,O
Rental,B-MISC
Agreement,L-MISC
and,O
all,O
the,O
keys,O
&,O
items,O
returned,O
as,O
mentioned,O
in,O
the,O
schedule,O
below,O
.,O
The,O
LESSEES,U-MISC
will,O
pay,O
to,O
the,O
LESSOR,U-MISC
10,O
%,O
increment,O
in,O
rent,O
on,O
completion,O
of,O
12,O
months,O
stay,O
from,O
the,O
date,O
of,O
this,O
agreement,O
.,O
The,O
LESSEE,U-ORG
will,O
pay,O
to,O
the,O
LESSOR,U-MISC
an,O
amount,O
appropriate,O
if,O
any,O
damage,O
/,O
wear,O
out,O
caused,O
to,O
the,O
premise,O
including,O
fittings,O
electrical,O
etc,O
at,O
the,O
time,O
of,O
the,O
tenancy,O
/,O
termination,O
of,O
the,O
agreement,O
.,O
The,O
LESSOR,U-ORG
holds,O
the,O
right,O
to,O
terminate,O
the,O
agreement,O
if,O
the,O
LESSEE,U-MISC
fails,O
to,O
pay,O
the,O
rent,O
regularly,O
for,O
consecutive,O
period,O
of,O
2,O
months,O
or,O
commits,O
a,O
breach,O
of,O
any,O
terms,O
herein,O
and,O
can,O
take,O
possession,O
of,O
the,O
premise,O
.,O
The,O
LESSEE,U-MISC
shall,O
use,O
the,O
premise,O
for,O
peaceful,O
&,O
residential,O
purpose,O
only,O
and,O
shall,O
not,O
do,O
any,O
alteration,O
without,O
the,O
Consent,O
of,O
the,O
LESSOR,O
.,O
Also,O
the,O
LESSEEE,U-MISC
will,O
not,O
sublet,O
',',O
underlet,O
',',O
part,O
let,O
or,O
part,O
with,O
the,O
possession,O
of,O
the,O
premise,O
.,O
The,O
LESSEE,B-ORG
&,I-ORG
LESSOR,L-ORG
both,O
have,O
retained,O
a,O
copy,O
of,O
this,O
agreement,O
.,O
SCHEDULE,O
The,O
premise,O
is,O
on,O
the,O
2nd,B-LOC
Floor,L-LOC
on,O
Site,O
#,O
82A,O
',',O
Vysya,B-LOC
Bank,I-LOC
Colony,L-LOC
',',O
ShantiniketanLyt,U-LOC
',',O
Arakere,B-LOC
Post,L-LOC
',',O
Bannerghatta,B-LOC
Road,L-LOC
',',O
Bangalore,U-LOC
560,O
0076,O
and,O
consists,O
of,O
one,O
hall,O
',',O
one,O
kitchen,O
',',O
one,O
bedroom,O
with,O
shelf,O
s,O
',',O
Bath,B-LOC
Room,L-LOC
with,O
electric,O
Geezer,O
',',O
one,O
two,O
wheeler,O
parking,O
at,O
the,O
ground,O
floor,O
',',O
Overheadtanks,O
',',O
Sumps,O
',',O
.,O
Complete,O
with,O
3Kw,O
AEH,O
power,O
electric,O
&,O
light,O
fittings,O
',',O
glazed,O
wall,O
tiles,O
in,O
bath,O
room,O
',',O
Granite,O
Floors,O
&,O
Slabs,O
in,O
the,O
kitchen,O
.,O
LESSOR,U-PER
LESSEE,O
ASHARAMESH,O
SADASIVUNI,O
DEEPTI,O
SADASHIVUNI,B-PER
KIRAN,L-PER
