words,tags
RENTAL,O
AGREEMENT,O
This,O
Rental,O
Agreement,O
is,O
made,O
and,O
executed,O
on,O
23,O
rd,O
day,O
of,O
May,O
Two,B-MISC
Thousand,I-MISC
Eleven,L-MISC
(,O
23-,O
05,O
-,O
2011,O
),O
M.V.,B-PER
Srinivas,L-PER
&,O
M.V.,B-LOC
Madhumathi,L-LOC
aged,O
54,O
years,O
&,O
42,O
Years,O
',',O
residing,O
at,O
No.40,O
',',O
7th,B-LOC
Cross,L-LOC
',',O
Shivanandanagar,U-LOC
',',O
Moodalapalya,U-LOC
',',O
Bangalore,U-LOC
-,O
560072,O
(,O
Here,O
in,O
after,O
referred,O
to,O
as,O
the,O
“,O
OWNER,O
”,O
of,O
the,O
first,B-ORG
Party,L-ORG
),O
on,O
the,O
first,O
part,O
and,O
;,O
M.V.,B-PER
Thirumalesh,L-PER
.,O
S,O
/,O
O.,O
Late,O
M.V.,B-PER
Venkataramaiah,L-PER
aged,O
about,O
32,O
years,O
',',O
residing,O
at,O
No.40,O
',',O
7th,B-LOC
Cross,L-LOC
',',O
Shivanandanagar,U-LOC
',',O
Moodalapalya,U-LOC
',',O
Bangalore,U-LOC
-,O
560072,O
(,O
Here,O
in,O
after,O
referred,O
to,O
as,O
the,O
TENANT,U-ORG
if,O
the,O
second,O
part,O
),O
The,O
Word,B-ORG
Owner,L-ORG
and,O
Tenant,O
shall,O
mean,O
and,O
include,O
their,O
respective,O
successors,O
',',O
legal,O
heirs,O
',',O
assignees,O
and,O
administrators,O
.,O
Whereas,O
the,O
First,B-ORG
Party,L-ORG
is,O
the,O
Absolute,B-ORG
Owner,L-ORG
and,O
in,O
possession,O
of,O
the,O
Schedule,O
property,O
Second,B-ORG
Party,L-ORG
“,O
TENANT,U-ORG
”,O
is,O
interested,O
to,O
take,O
the,O
schedule,O
premises,O
on,O
rent,O
and,O
the,O
Owner,U-ORG
interested,O
to,O
give,O
the,O
schedule,O
premises,O
on,O
the,O
rent,O
on,O
the,O
following,O
terms,O
and,O
conditions:-,O
NOW,O
THIS,O
INDENTURE,O
OF,O
AGREEMENT,O
IS,O
WITNESSETH,O
AS,O
FOLLOWS:-,O
The,O
Tenant,O
has,O
this,O
day,O
paid,O
a,O
sum,O
of,O
Rs,U-MISC
.,O
'50,000/-',O
(,O
Rupees,O
Fifty,O
Thousand,O
Only,O
),O
to,O
the,O
Owner,U-ORG
as,O
Rent,O
deposit,O
and,O
the,O
rent,O
deposit,O
shall,O
not,O
carry,O
any,O
interest,O
The,B-ORG
Tenant,L-ORG
agrees,O
to,O
pay,O
a,O
monthly,O
rent,O
of,O
Rs,O
.,O
'4,200/-',O
(,O
Rupees,O
Four,O
Thousand,O
Two,O
Hundred,O
Only,O
),O
to,O
the,O
owner,O
on,O
or,O
before,O
5th,O
of,O
every,O
month,O
without,O
fail,O
.,O
If,O
fails,O
to,O
pay,O
for,O
a,O
period,O
of,O
2,O
months,O
the,O
owner,O
can,O
occupy,O
the,O
house,O
premises,O
.,O
The,O
rent,O
shall,O
be,O
increased,O
by,O
5,O
%,O
(,O
Five,O
Percent,O
),O
once,O
in,O
every,O
one,O
year,O
.,O
The,O
Tenant,U-ORG
shall,O
pay,O
the,O
electricity,O
charges,O
and,O
water,O
charges,O
regularly,O
for,O
his,O
Consumption,O
.,O
That,O
the,O
Tenant,U-MISC
shall,O
not,O
sublet,O
or,O
underlet,O
or,O
part,O
with,O
any,O
portion,O
of,O
the,O
Scheduled,O
house,O
premises,O
.,O
That,O
the,O
Tenant,U-ORG
shall,O
maintain,O
the,O
Scheduled,O
premises,O
and,O
the,O
surrounding,O
in,O
Good,O
and,O
hygiene,O
condition,O
.,O
Three,O
months,O
advance,O
notice,O
has,O
to,O
be,O
given,O
by,O
both,O
the,O
Tenant,B-ORG
and,L-ORG
the,O
Owner,O
for,O
The,O
said,O
house,O
premises,O
.,O
No,O
Compensation,O
has,O
to,O
be,O
claimed,O
by,O
the,O
Tenant,U-ORG
during,O
the,O
period,O
of,O
vacating,O
his,O
scheduled,O
house,O
premises,O
.,O
The,O
Tenant,O
shall,O
not,O
damage,O
or,O
misplace,O
any,O
of,O
the,O
fittings,O
and,O
fixtures,O
thereon,O
',',O
if,O
.,O
Anything,O
is,O
found,O
to,O
be,O
default/,O
misplaced,O
.,O
The,O
tenant,O
shall,O
rectify/,O
replace,O
the,O
Same,O
if,O
fails,O
to,O
do,O
so,O
',',O
the,O
owner,O
is,O
empowered,O
to,O
deduct,O
the,O
cost,O
of,O
the,O
same,O
from,O
The,O
security,O
deposit,O
.,O
So,O
paid,O
by,O
the,O
tenant,O
to,O
the,O
owner,O
.,O
That,O
the,O
duration,O
of,O
this,O
Agreement,U-MISC
is,O
for,O
a,O
period,O
of,O
11,O
(,O
Eleven,O
),O
Months,O
subject,O
to,O
succeeding,O
English,U-MISC
calendar,O
month,O
.,O
All,O
the,O
terms,O
and,O
conditions,O
are,O
agreed,O
as,O
stated,O
above,O
.,O
Portico,O
remains,O
a,O
common,O
parking,O
space,O
and,O
the,O
tenant,O
should,O
Not,O
occupy,O
for,O
any,O
Other,O
purpose,O
without,O
the,O
permission,O
of,O
the,O
owner,O
.,O
SCHEDULE,O
All,O
that,O
piece,O
of,O
parcel,O
of,O
the,O
house,O
premises,O
(,O
I,O
Floor,O
),O
bearing,O
No.40,O
',',O
7th,B-LOC
Cross,L-LOC
',',O
Shivanandanagar,U-LOC
',',O
Moodalapalya,U-LOC
',',O
Bangalore,U-LOC
-,O
560072,O
consisting,O
of,O
One,B-LOC
Hall,L-LOC
',',O
One,B-LOC
Bed,I-LOC
Room,L-LOC
',',O
&,O
one,O
Kitchen,O
.,O
In,O
witness,O
where,O
of,O
the,O
Owner,B-ORG
and,I-ORG
Tenant,L-ORG
have,O
set,O
their,O
hands,O
and,O
signed,O
this,O
agreement,O
of,O
rent,O
on,O
the,O
day,O
',',O
month,O
and,O
year,O
above,O
mentioned,O
at,O
Bangalore,U-LOC
.,O
WITNESSES,O
:,O
1,O
.,O
(,O
M.V.,B-PER
Srinivas,L-PER
&,O
M.V.,B-PER
Madhumathi,L-PER
),O
OWNER,O
(,O
M.V.,B-PER
Thirumalesh,L-PER
),O
TENANT,U-ORG
