words,tags
AGREEMENT,O
This,O
Agreement,O
is,O
entered,O
into,O
Date-7/2/08,U-MISC
',',O
between,O
Procall,B-ORG
Private,I-ORG
Limited,L-ORG
having,O
its,O
Corporate,B-ORG
Office,L-ORG
at,O
Procall,B-ORG
Private,I-ORG
Limited,L-ORG
#,O
F-6,U-MISC
.,O
First,O
floor,O
.,O
Triveni,B-ORG
Commercial,I-ORG
Complex,L-ORG
.,O
Shiekh,B-ORG
Sarai,L-ORG
Phase-1,O
.,O
New,B-MISC
Delhi-1100,L-MISC
17,O
hereinafter,O
referred,O
to,O
as,O
",O
Procall,U-MISC
",O
(,O
which,O
expression,O
shall,O
unless,O
repugnant,O
to,O
the,O
context,O
or,O
meaning,O
thereof,O
includes,O
its,O
successors,O
',',O
associates,O
',',O
business,O
affiliates,O
',',O
subsidiaries,O
and,O
assigns,O
),O
of,O
the,O
one,O
part,O
and,O
Address,O
of,O
the,O
Party,B-ORG
M,L-ORG
/,O
s,O
Telelogic,B-ORG
India,I-ORG
Pvt,L-ORG
.,O
Ltd.,U-ORG
#,O
72,O
Salarpuria,U-LOC
pearl,O
civil,O
station,O
.,O
Residency,O
road,O
.,O
Bangalore,U-LOC
560025hereinafter,O
referred,O
to,O
as,O
",O
User,U-MISC
",O
(,O
which,O
expression,O
shall,O
unless,O
repugnant,O
to,O
the,O
context,O
or,O
meaning,O
thereof,O
includes,O
its,O
heirs,O
',',O
legal,O
representatives,O
',',O
successors,O
and,O
assigns,O
),O
of,O
the,O
other,O
part,O
and,O
Whereas,O
the,O
User,U-MISC
has,O
approached,O
Procall,U-ORG
for,O
Renting,B-ORG
Trunking,I-ORG
Radio,I-ORG
Services,L-ORG
under,O
the,O
terms,O
and,O
conditions,O
contemplated,O
by,O
this,O
Agreement,U-MISC
.,O
NOW,O
THEREFORE,O
THE,O
PARTIES,O
HERETO,U-PER
AGREE,O
AS,O
FOLLOWS,O
1,O
.,O
SECURITY,O
DEPOSIT,O
The,O
user,O
agrees,O
to,O
pay,O
an,O
amount,O
of,O
Rs,U-MISC
6000/-,O
as,O
an,O
interest,O
free,O
security,O
deposit,O
in,O
Procall,B-ORG
Pvt,L-ORG
.,O
Ltd.,U-ORG
This,O
will,O
be,O
deposited,O
in,O
the,O
bank,O
by,O
Procall,B-ORG
Pvt,L-ORG
.,O
Ltd.,U-ORG
and,O
shall,O
be,O
returned,O
to,O
the,O
user,O
on,O
the,O
expiry,O
of,O
the,O
rental,O
period,O
after,O
they,O
return,O
the,O
radios,O
',',O
Accessories,O
and,O
any,O
other,O
material,O
belonging,O
to,O
Procall,B-ORG
Pvt,L-ORG
.,O
Ltd,U-ORG
',',O
Which,O
they,O
have,O
taken,O
on,O
rent,O
in,O
good,O
order,O
and,O
condition,O
(,O
To,O
be,O
confirmed,O
by,O
Procall,U-ORG
after,O
inspection,O
at,O
their,O
premises,O
),O
2,O
..,O
RENTAL,O
PERIOD,O
The,O
User,O
agrees,O
to,O
rent,O
radios,O
from,O
Procall,U-ORG
for,O
a,O
minimum,O
period,O
of,O
12,O
months,O
.,O
The,O
start,O
date,O
of,O
Rental,O
period,O
will,O
be,O
the,O
date,O
from,O
which,O
Radios,U-MISC
will,O
be,O
activated,O
.,O
SCHEME,O
OF,O
RENTAL,O
The,O
customer,O
would,O
be,O
required,O
to,O
use,O
Procall,U-MISC
services,O
for,O
a,O
minimum,O
period,O
of,O
12,O
billed,O
months,O
.,O
This,O
period,O
would,O
be,O
considered,O
as,O
locking,O
period,O
for,O
the,O
agreement,O
.,O
During,O
the,O
Rental,O
period,O
the,O
Radios,O
will,O
remain,O
the,O
absolute,O
properly,O
of,O
Procall,U-ORG
.,O
In,O
case,O
of,O
discontinuity,O
of,O
the,O
rental,O
services,O
or,O
non,O
payment,O
/,O
dishonour,O
of,O
cheques,O
or,O
any,O
other,O
such,O
event,O
',',O
the,O
Radio,U-MISC
shall,O
be,O
repossessed,O
by,O
Procall,U-ORG
for,O
which,O
no,O
credit,O
will,O
be,O
given,O
to,O
the,O
User,U-MISC
.,O
In,O
case,O
of,O
loss,O
',',O
damage,O
or,O
theft,O
',',O
the,O
User,U-MISC
shall,O
be,O
liable,O
to,O
reimburse,O
the,O
cost,O
of,O
the,O
equipment,O
less,O
depreciation,O
(,O
i,O
.e,O
.,O
20,O
%,O
W.D.V,U-MISC
),O
to,O
Procall,U-ORG
.,O
Procall,U-ORG
shall,O
switch,O
off,O
the,O
lost,O
Radio,U-ORG
immediately,O
on,O
written,O
information,O
by,O
the,O
user,O
mentioning,O
the,O
UFMI,U-ORG
(,O
user,O
fleet,O
member,O
ID,O
),O
of,O
the,O
radio,O
.,O
The,O
cost,O
of,O
Radio,U-ORG
',',O
for,O
the,O
above,O
purpose,O
has,O
been,O
fixed,O
at,O
Rs,U-MISC
.,O
12000/-,O
(,O
Rupees,O
Twelve,O
Thousand,O
only,O
),O
per,O
set,O
.,O
Although,O
Procall,U-ORG
is,O
obliged,O
to,O
provide,O
the,O
service,O
in,O
accordance,O
with,O
the,O
terms,O
and,O
conditions,O
of,O
this,O
agreement,O
',',O
it,O
shall,O
not,O
be,O
responsible,O
for,O
any,O
damages,O
where,O
the,O
continuity,O
of,O
the,O
service,O
is,O
affected,O
by,O
reasons,O
of,O
Acts,B-MISC
of,I-MISC
God,L-MISC
',',O
natural,O
calamity,O
',',O
fire,O
',',O
Strikes,O
',',O
Riots,O
',',O
Govemment,O
/,O
Statutory,O
Order,O
or,O
Restrictions,O
and/or,O
such,O
other,O
events,O
outside,O
Procall,U-ORG
'''s',O
control,O
.,O
During,O
the,O
useful,O
life,O
of,O
the,O
Radios,U-MISC
',',O
they,O
remain,O
property,O
of,O
Procall,B-ORG
Private,I-ORG
Limited,L-ORG
.,O
AIR,B-ORG
TIME,L-ORG
AND,O
RENTAL,O
CHARGES,O
ON,O
RADIO,O
The,O
User,O
agrees,O
to,O
take,O
Radios,O
on,O
rent,O
from,O
Procall,B-ORG
Private,I-ORG
Limited,L-ORG
.,O
The,O
rentals,O
will,O
be,O
charged,O
@,O
Rs,O
.,O
1200/-,O
per,O
unit,O
per,O
month,O
payable,O
monthly,O
in,O
advance,O
.,O
Service,O
Tax,O
will,O
be,O
charged,O
@,O
12.36,O
%,O
.,O
Incase,O
of,O
any,O
new,O
Taxes,O
are,O
incorporated,O
by,O
Government,B-ORG
of,I-ORG
India,L-ORG
or,O
State,B-ORG
Government,L-ORG
;,O
the,O
same,O
would,O
be,O
communicated,O
separately,O
.,O
e.,O
This,O
agreement,O
is,O
valid,O
for,O
quantity,O
upto,O
100,O
radios,O
.,O
PAYMENT,O
TERMS,O
Work,O
Order,O
along,O
with,O
one,O
month,O
service,O
in,O
advance,O
in,O
favor,O
of,O
ProCall,B-ORG
Private,I-ORG
Limited,L-ORG
.,O
Rental,O
Payment,O
payable,O
monthly,O
in,O
advance,O
in,O
favor,O
of,O
ProCall,B-ORG
Private,I-ORG
Limited,L-ORG
.,O
Service,O
Maintenance,O
All,O
hardware,O
related,O
issues,O
to,O
be,O
reported,O
/,O
repaired,O
at,O
Motorola,B-ORG
Authorized,L-ORG
service,O
centre,O
in,O
Bangalore,U-LOC
.,O
The,O
contact,O
for,O
the,O
same,O
will,O
be,O
:,O
M,O
/,O
s,O
Redington,B-LOC
India,L-LOC
#,O
122/2,O
',',O
Infantry,B-LOC
Road,L-LOC
',',O
Monarch,B-LOC
Chambers,L-LOC
',',O
2nd,O
floor,O
',',O
Bangalore,U-LOC
.,O
Any,B-ORG
Network,L-ORG
service,O
related,O
issues,O
will,O
be,O
addressed,O
by,O
Procall,B-ORG
Private,I-ORG
Limited,L-ORG
.,O
ACCESSORIES,U-ORG
All,O
spare,O
batteries,O
and,O
other,O
related,O
accessories,O
will,O
be,O
purchased,O
by,O
Telelogic,B-ORG
India,I-ORG
Pvt,L-ORG
.,O
Ltd,U-ORG
directly,O
from,O
the,O
Motorola,B-ORG
Authorized,I-ORG
Repair,I-ORG
Centre,L-ORG
for,O
the,O
purpose,O
of,O
using,O
Radios,U-MISC
on,O
rental,O
.,O
COMPLETION,O
On,O
expiry,O
of,O
the,O
rental,O
period,O
or,O
termination,O
of,O
the,O
agreement,O
',',O
the,O
User,U-MISC
shall,O
immediately,O
handover,O
the,O
possession,O
of,O
the,O
Radios,O
to,O
Procall,B-ORG
Private,I-ORG
Limited,L-ORG
along,O
with,O
the,O
cheque,O
of,O
rental,O
usage,O
period,O
.,O
TERMINATION,O
On,O
Completion,O
of,O
12,O
months,O
paid,O
billing,O
',',O
either,O
party,O
can,O
exit,O
from,O
the,O
agreement,O
by,O
giving,O
a,O
30,O
days,O
notice,O
period,O
.,O
In,O
case,O
Customer,O
decides,O
to,O
terminate,O
the,O
agreement,O
before,O
completion,O
of,O
12,O
paid,O
months,O
',',O
the,O
customer,O
will,O
be,O
liable,O
to,O
pay,O
Procall,U-ORG
for,O
the,O
balance,O
months,O
of,O
services,O
.,O
In,O
the,O
event,O
of,O
termination,O
',',O
the,O
termination,O
would,O
be,O
applicable,O
on,O
receipt,O
of,O
complete,O
radios,O
along,O
with,O
accessories,O
by,O
Procall,U-ORG
or,O
any,O
of,O
its,O
representatives,O
.,O
CONSF.Ot,O
JF.NCF.S,O
OF,O
DISHONOUR,O
OF,O
CHEQUES,O
The,O
User,O
hereby,O
undertakes,O
that,O
he,O
fully,O
understands,O
and,O
is,O
aware,O
of,O
the,O
consequences,O
of,O
dishonour,O
of,O
cheque,O
',',O
which,O
are,O
enumerated,O
as,O
per,O
",O
Section,B-MISC
138,L-MISC
of,O
the,O
negotiable,B-MISC
Instrument,I-MISC
Act,L-MISC
',',O
1881,O
.,O
ARBITRATION,O
In,O
case,O
of,O
dispute,O
arising,O
out,O
of,O
',',O
or,O
in,O
relation,O
to,O
this,O
Agreement,U-MISC
between,O
the,O
parties,O
hereto,O
the,O
same,O
shall,O
first,O
be,O
sought,O
to,O
be,O
settled,O
by,O
arbitration,O
governed,O
by,O
the,O
Arbitration,B-ORG
and,I-ORG
Conciliation,I-ORG
Act,L-ORG
',',O
1996,O
and,O
the,O
rules,O
framed,O
hereunder,O
.,O
JURISDICTION,O
All,O
disputes,O
arising,O
out,O
or,O
in,O
any,O
way,O
connected,O
with,O
this,O
Agreement,U-MISC
shall,O
be,O
deemed,O
to,O
have,O
arisen,O
in,O
Delhi,U-LOC
/,O
New,B-LOC
Delhi,L-LOC
and,O
only,O
the,O
courts,O
in,O
the,O
State,B-ORG
of,I-ORG
Delhi,L-ORG
shall,O
have,O
jurisdiction,O
to,O
determine,O
the,O
same,O
.,O
All,O
associated,O
cost,O
',',O
incidental,O
to,O
the,O
execution,O
of,O
this,O
agreement,O
will,O
be,O
borne,O
by,O
Procall,U-ORG
and,O
shall,O
not,O
be,O
reimbursed,O
by,O
the,O
User,U-MISC
.,O
The,O
charges,O
by,O
Procall,U-ORG
are,O
fixed,O
for,O
the,O
period,O
of,O
12,O
months,O
and,O
no,O
enhanced,O
charges,O
will,O
be,O
payable,O
by,O
the,O
User,U-MISC
.,O
Apart,O
from,O
any,O
new,O
Govt,O
',',O
levies,O
&,O
Taxes,O
.,O
.The,O
User,U-MISC
expressly,O
agrees,O
to,O
pay,O
sales,O
tax,O
',',O
service,O
tax,O
and,O
such,O
other,O
taxes,O
',',O
cess,O
and,O
levies,O
imposed,O
by,O
State,O
/,O
central,O
government,O
',',O
municipal,O
or,O
local,O
authorities,O
whenever,O
they,O
become,O
leviable,O
at,O
any,O
point,O
.,O
(,O
As,O
on,O
date,O
Taxes,O
are,O
Service,O
Tax,O
@12.36,O
%,O
on,O
Rental,O
Charges,O
.,O
),O
IN,O
WITNESS,O
WHEREOF,O
the,O
parties,O
have,O
hereto,O
put,O
their,O
hands,O
on,O
this,O
day,O
',',O
month,O
and,O
year,O
herein,O
above,O
written,O
.,O
For,O
and,O
on,O
behalf,O
of,O
For,O
and,O
on,O
behalf,O
of,O
PROCALL,U-ORG
PRIVATE,O
LIMITED,O
Telelogic,B-ORG
India,I-ORG
Private,I-ORG
Limited,L-ORG
(,O
Authorised,B-ORG
Signatory,L-ORG
),O
(,O
Authorised,O
Signatory,O
),O
Date,O
and,O
Stamp,O
WITNESS,O
