words,tags
House,O
Rental,O
Contract,O
KNOWN,O
ALL,O
MEN,O
BY,O
THESE,O
PRESENTS,O
:,O
This,O
House,O
Rental,O
Contract,O
',',O
made,O
and,O
entered,O
into,O
this,O
20th,O
day,O
of,O
May,O
2007,O
at,O
Manila,U-LOC
by,O
and,O
between,O
:,O
Antonio,B-PER
Levy,I-PER
S.,I-PER
Ingles,L-PER
.,O
Jr.,O
and/or,O
Mary,B-PER
Rose,I-PER
C.,I-PER
Ingles,L-PER
',',O
of,O
legal,O
age,O
',',O
with,O
residence,O
and,O
postal,O
address,O
at,O
Unit,O
2006,O
EGI,B-LOC
Taft,I-LOC
Tower,L-LOC
2339,O
Taft,B-LOC
Avenue,L-LOC
',',O
Malate,U-LOC
',',O
Manila,U-LOC
',',O
And,O
herein,O
referred,O
to,O
as,O
the,O
Owner(s,O
),O
',',O
—,O
And,O
—,O
GERALDINE,O
O.,B-PER
GALINATO,L-PER
.,O
of,O
legal,O
age,O
',',O
with,O
residence,O
and,O
postal,O
address,O
at,O
6,O
Manganese,B-LOC
Road,L-LOC
',',O
Pilar,B-LOC
Village,L-LOC
',',O
Las,B-LOC
Pinas,L-LOC
',',O
Metro,B-LOC
Manila,L-LOC
',',O
And,O
herein,O
referred,O
to,O
as,O
the,O
Resident(s,O
),O
',',O
WITNESSETH,O
:,O
In,O
consideration,O
of,O
the,O
agreements,O
of,O
the,O
Resident(s,U-MISC
),O
',',O
known,O
as,O
:,O
GERALDINE,B-PER
O.,I-PER
GALINATO,L-PER
.,O
the,O
Owner(s,O
),O
',',O
known,O
as,O
:,O
Antonio,B-PER
Levy,I-PER
S.,I-PER
Ingles,L-PER
.,O
Jr.,U-PER
and/or,O
Mary,B-PER
Rose,I-PER
C.,I-PER
Ingles,L-PER
',',O
hereby,O
rent,O
their,O
the,O
dwelling,O
/,O
house,O
located,O
at,O
Lot,B-LOC
6,L-LOC
',',O
Block,B-LOC
20,L-LOC
',',O
Royal,B-LOC
South,I-LOC
Townhomes,L-LOC
',',O
Marcos,B-LOC
Alvarez,I-LOC
Avenue,L-LOC
',',O
Talon,U-LOC
5,O
',',O
Las,B-LOC
Pinas,I-LOC
City,L-LOC
',',O
Metro,B-LOC
Manila,L-LOC
for,O
the,O
period,O
commencing,O
on,O
the,O
20th,O
day,O
of,O
May,O
',',O
2007,O
',',O
and,O
monthly,O
thereafter,O
until,O
the,O
20th,O
day,O
of,O
May,O
',',O
2008,O
',',O
at,O
which,O
time,O
this,O
Agreement,U-MISC
is,O
terminated,O
.,O
Resident(s,U-ORG
),O
',',O
in,O
consideration,O
of,O
Owner(s,U-ORG
),O
permitting,O
them,O
to,O
occupy,O
the,O
above,O
property,O
',',O
hereby,O
agrees,O
to,O
the,O
following,O
terms,O
:,O
RENT,O
:,O
To,O
pay,O
as,O
rental,O
the,O
sum,O
of,O
SIX,O
THOUSAND,O
FIVE,O
HUNDRED,O
PESOS,O
IP,O
6.500.001,O
per,O
month,O
',',O
due,O
and,O
payable,O
in,O
advance,O
from,O
the,O
20th,O
day,O
of,O
every,O
month,O
.,O
FAILURE,O
TO,O
PAY,O
ON,O
TIME,O
:,O
Failure,O
to,O
pay,O
the,O
rent,O
will,O
result,O
in,O
being,O
served,O
a,O
Notice,O
to,O
End,B-ORG
Residential,I-ORG
Tenancy,L-ORG
.,O
This,O
Notice,O
may,O
be,O
served,O
if,O
you,O
have,O
an,O
outstanding,O
balance,O
from,O
failure,O
to,O
pay,O
your,O
rent,O
.,O
This,O
Notice,O
may,O
also,O
be,O
served,O
from,O
being,O
habitually,O
late,O
in,O
paying,O
your,O
rent,O
regardless,O
of,O
the,O
balance,O
owed,O
.,O
Once,O
the,O
Notice,O
to,O
End,B-ORG
Residential,I-ORG
Tenancy,L-ORG
is,O
received,O
',',O
you,O
will,O
have,O
a,O
prescribed,O
time,O
to,O
pay,O
all,O
of,O
the,O
amount,O
overdue,O
on,O
your,O
rent,O
.,O
A,O
three,O
-,O
dav,O
grace,O
period,O
will,O
be,O
allowed,O
for,O
late,O
payment,O
.,O
Failure,O
to,O
pay,O
the,O
monthly,O
rental,O
within,O
the,O
grace,O
period,O
is,O
subject,O
to,O
FIVE,O
(,O
5,O
%,O
),O
PERCENT,O
interest,O
per,O
month,O
of,O
delay,O
as,O
penalty,O
.,O
Habitual,O
failure,O
of,O
the,O
Resident(s,U-MISC
),O
to,O
pay,O
within,O
the,O
prescribed,O
time,O
shall,O
result,O
in,O
the,O
Owner(s,U-ORG
),O
taking,O
immediate,O
legal,O
action,O
to,O
evict,O
the,O
Resident(s,U-ORG
),O
from,O
the,O
premises,O
and,O
seize,O
the,O
security,O
deposit,O
.,O
SECURITY,O
DEPOSIT,O
:,O
Resident(s,O
),O
agrees,O
to,O
pay,O
a,O
deposit,O
in,O
the,O
amount,O
of,O
SIX,O
THOUSAND,O
FIVE,O
HUNDRED,O
PESOS,O
(,O
P,O
6.500.001,O
to,O
secure,O
Resident(s,O
),O
’s,O
pledge,O
of,O
full,O
compliance,O
with,O
the,O
terms,O
of,O
this,O
agreement,O
.,O
Note,O
:,O
THE,O
DEPOSIT,O
MAY,O
NOT,O
BE,O
USED,O
BY,O
TENANT,O
TO,O
PAY,O
THE,O
RENT,O
DURING,O
THE,O
TENANCY,O
.,O
The,O
security,O
deposit,O
will,O
be,O
used,O
at,O
the,O
end,O
of,O
the,O
tenancy,O
to,O
compensate,O
the,O
Owner(s,U-MISC
),O
for,O
any,O
damages,O
or,O
unpaid,O
rent,O
or,O
charges,O
',',O
and,O
will,O
be,O
repaired,O
or,O
replaced,O
at,O
Resident(s,U-ORG
),O
’s,O
expense,O
with,O
funds,O
other,O
than,O
the,O
deposit,O
.,O
METHOD,O
OF,O
PAYMENT,O
:,O
The,O
initial,O
advance,O
payment,O
of,O
rent,O
and,O
deposit,O
under,O
this,O
contract,O
be,O
PAID,O
IN,O
CASH,O
at,O
least,O
7,O
days,O
before,O
the,O
date,O
of,O
moving,O
-,O
in,O
.,O
Thereafter,O
',',O
monthly,O
rent,O
payments,O
must,O
be,O
paid,O
by,O
POST,O
DATED,O
CHECKS,O
payable,O
to,O
ANTONIO,U-PER
LEVY,O
S.,O
INGLES,O
.,O
JR,O
.,O
until,O
a,O
first,O
check,O
is,O
dishonored,O
and,O
returned,O
unpaid,O
.,O
Regardless,O
of,O
cause,O
',',O
no,O
other,O
additional,O
payments,O
may,O
afterwards,O
be,O
made,O
by,O
check,O
.,O
Checks,O
returned,O
will,O
not,O
be,O
redeposited,O
.,O
The,O
Resident(s,O
),O
will,O
be,O
notified,O
by,O
a,O
3,O
day,O
notice,O
',',O
and,O
will,O
be,O
required,O
to,O
pay,O
the,O
amount,O
due,O
in,O
cash,O
.,O
