words,tags
RENTAL,O
AGREEMENT,O
This,O
RENTAL,O
AGREEMENT,O
is,O
made,O
and,O
executed,O
at,O
Bangalore,U-LOC
',',O
on,O
this,O
5th,O
day,O
of,O
April,O
',',O
2012,O
',',O
between,O
Mrs,O
',',O
PADMAVATI,U-LOC
',',O
'154/2,1st',O
floor,O
',',O
9th,B-LOC
Cross,L-LOC
',',O
Byrasandra,B-LOC
Main,I-LOC
Road,L-LOC
',',O
G,B-LOC
M,I-LOC
Palya,L-LOC
',',O
Bangalore,U-LOC
-,O
560,O
075,O
.,O
hereinafter,O
called,O
the,O
‘,O
OWNER,O
’,O
of,O
one,O
part,O
Mrs.,O
SANGHAMITRA,B-LOC
PARIDA,L-LOC
',',O
Working,O
at,O
:,O
Sasken,B-ORG
CommunicationTechnologies,I-ORG
Ltd,L-ORG
',',O
139/25,O
',',O
Ring,B-LOC
Road,L-LOC
',',O
Domlur,B-LOC
Bangalore,L-LOC
560,O
071,O
',',O
hereinafter,O
called,O
the,O
‘,O
TENANT,U-MISC
’,O
of,O
the,O
other,O
part,O
.,O
Whereas,O
the,O
Tenant,O
has,O
Requested,O
the,O
Owner,O
to,O
let,O
out,O
a,O
house,O
',',O
154/2,O
',',O
Ground,B-LOC
floor,L-LOC
',',O
9th,B-LOC
Cross,L-LOC
',',O
Byrasandra,B-LOC
Main,I-LOC
Road,L-LOC
',',O
G,B-LOC
M,I-LOC
Palya,L-LOC
',',O
Bangalore,U-LOC
-,O
560,O
075,O
.In,O
consideration,O
of,O
the,O
rent,O
hereinafter,O
reserved,O
and,O
the,O
condition,O
herein,O
after,O
stated,O
NOW,O
THIS,O
AGREEMENT,O
WITNESSETH,O
AS,O
FOLLOWS,O
:,O
The,O
Tenant,O
shall,O
pay,O
a,O
monthly,O
rent,O
of,O
Rs.8000,O
on,O
or,O
before,O
5th,O
of,O
every,O
month,O
.,O
Rent,O
will,O
be,O
start,O
from,O
at,O
the,O
time,O
of,O
occupation,O
The,O
rent,O
enhancement,O
shall,O
be,O
increased,O
at,O
10,O
%,O
after,O
11,O
months,O
The,O
Tenant,U-ORG
has,O
to,O
pay,O
the,O
security,O
deposit,O
amount,O
of,O
Rs,U-MISC
.,O
60000.The,O
Tenant,O
paid,O
cash,O
Rs.60000/-,O
Dated,O
:,O
05/04/2012,O
will,O
be,O
paid,O
at,O
time,O
of,O
occupation,O
The,O
owner,O
acknowledges,O
the,O
receipt,O
of,O
the,O
same,O
.,O
The,O
security,O
deposit,O
amount,O
of,O
Rs,U-MISC
.,O
60000,O
shall,O
not,O
carry,O
any,O
interest,O
but,O
will,O
be,O
refundable,O
to,O
the,O
Tenant,U-ORG
on,O
the,O
termination,O
of,O
Tenancy,U-ORG
.,O
After,O
deducting,O
any,O
dues,O
in,O
rent,O
/,O
electricity,O
/,O
damages,O
etc,O
.,O
',',O
The,O
Tenancy,O
shall,O
be,O
in,O
force,O
for,O
the,O
period,O
of,O
(,O
11,O
),O
Months,O
from,O
the,O
5th,O
April,O
of,O
2012,O
.,O
month,O
of,O
tenancy,O
being,O
the,O
English,B-MISC
Calendar,L-MISC
month,O
.,O
The,O
owner,O
shall,O
have,O
the,O
right,O
to,O
terminate,O
the,O
tenancy,O
if,O
the,O
tenant,O
fails,O
to,O
pay,O
the,O
rent,O
regularly,O
for,O
a,O
consecutive,O
period,O
of,O
two,O
months,O
or,O
commits,O
breach,O
of,O
any,O
of,O
the,O
terms,O
herein,O
and,O
take,O
possession,O
of,O
the,O
premises,O
.,O
The,O
Tenant,O
shall,O
use,O
the,O
premises,O
only,O
for,O
Residential,O
purpose,O
and,O
shall,O
not,O
use,O
it,O
any,O
offensive,O
or,O
objectionable,O
purposes,O
business,O
etc,O
.,O
without,O
permission,O
of,O
the,O
Owner,O
.,O
The,O
Tenant,O
shall,O
keep,O
the,O
premises,O
neatly,O
in,O
tenentable,O
condition,O
and,O
shall,O
not,O
make,O
any,O
alteration,O
therein,O
without,O
permission,O
of,O
the,O
Owner,U-ORG
.,O
Also,O
any,O
damges,O
happened,O
during,O
the,O
stay,O
',',O
the,O
cost,O
for,O
the,O
damages,O
and,O
assocites,O
expenses,O
shall,O
be,O
recovered,O
in,O
the,O
advance,O
or,O
extra,O
.,O
The,O
Tenant,O
shall,O
pay,O
Electricity,O
and,O
water,O
charges,O
separately,O
to,O
the,O
concerned,O
authority,O
and,O
the,O
owner,O
shall,O
pay,O
the,O
property,O
taxes,O
.,O
The,O
tenancy,O
may,O
be,O
renewed,O
for,O
further,O
period,O
/,O
s,O
mutually,O
agreed,O
between,O
the,O
parties,O
on,O
the,O
terms,O
and,O
conditions,O
to,O
be,O
specified,O
at,O
that,O
time,O
.,O
It,O
is,O
hereby,O
agreed,O
that,O
one,O
-,O
month,O
notice,O
on,O
either,O
side,O
is,O
required,O
for,O
the,O
termination,O
of,O
tenancy,O
.,O
The,O
tenant,O
shall,O
pay,O
one,O
month,O
rent,O
towards,O
painting,O
and,O
cleaning,O
charges,O
at,O
the,O
time,O
of,O
vacating,O
the,O
schedule,O
premises,O
.,O
The,O
foilwing,O
fixures,O
and,O
accesariesr,O
are,O
provided,O
by,O
the,O
owner,O
in,O
good,O
condition,O
',',O
the,O
same,O
shall,O
be,O
in,O
operatable,O
conditions,O
while,O
leaving,O
.,O
Ceiling,O
fans,O
-,O
Khaitan,U-ORG
3,O
Nos,B-ORG
Tube,L-ORG
lights,O
-,O
Surya,U-ORG
3,O
Nos,B-ORG
Exhaust,L-ORG
fans,O
1,O
No,O
Bulbs,O
5,O
Nos,O
SCHEDULE,O
All,O
the,O
piece,O
and,O
parcel,O
of,O
the,O
house,O
premises,O
',',O
154/2,O
',',O
Ground,O
floor,O
',',O
9th,B-LOC
Cross,L-LOC
',',O
Byrasandra,B-LOC
Main,I-LOC
Road,L-LOC
',',O
G,B-LOC
M,I-LOC
Palya,L-LOC
',',O
Bangalore,U-LOC
-,O
560,O
075,O
.,O
consisting,O
of,O
:,O
1,O
Hall,U-LOC
',',O
1,O
Kitchen,U-LOC
',',O
2,O
Bed,O
rooms,O
',',O
1,O
Bath,B-ORG
&,I-ORG
Toilet,L-ORG
.,O
',',O
IN,O
WITNESS,O
WHEREOF,O
the,O
parties,O
have,O
set,O
their,O
respective,O
hands,O
unto,O
this,O
agreement,O
',',O
the,O
day,O
and,O
year,O
first,O
above,O
written,O
.,O
WITNESSES,O
:,O
1,O
.,O
OWNER,B-ORG
TENANT,L-ORG
