words,tags
RENTAL-,O
AGREEMENT,O
This,O
RENTAL,O
AGREEMENT,O
IS,O
made,O
and,O
executed,O
on,O
06th,O
day,O
of,O
March,O
2013,O
at,O
Hyderabad,U-LOC
.,O
By,O
and,O
between,O
Smt,B-PER
C.BHAGYAMMA,L-PER
',',O
w/o,O
C.GOVARDHAN,B-PER
REDDY,L-PER
',',O
age,O
about,O
52,O
years,O
.,O
Occ,O
:,O
Housewife,O
R,O
/,O
O,O
H.N04,O
-,O
8,O
-,O
38,O
',',O
Manjeera,B-PER
Nagar,L-PER
',',O
Sangareddy,B-PER
Mandal,L-PER
',',O
Medak,B-PER
District,L-PER
',',O
AP,U-ORG
.,O
HEREINAFTER,U-PER
CALLED,O
THE,O
FIRST,O
PARTY,O
THE,O
“,O
OWNER,O
”,O
WHICH,O
TERM,O
SHALL,O
MEAN,O
AND,O
INCLUDE,O
ALL,O
HIS,O
HER,O
HEIRS,O
EXECUTORS,O
.,O
ADMINISTRATORS,O
LEGAL,O
REPRESENTATIVES,O
AND,O
ASSIGNEES,O
AND,O
M,O
/,O
S.,B-ORG
JP,I-ORG
INTERIO,L-ORG
',',O
M,O
/,O
S.SRI,B-ORG
JAYAM,L-ORG
HOUSING,O
&,O
CONSTRUCTIONS,O
&,O
M,O
/,O
S.SRI,B-ORG
JAYAM,L-ORG
HOUSING,O
&,O
CONSTRUCTIONS,O
Pvt,O
.,O
Ltd,U-ORG
.,O
represented,O
by,O
its,O
Managing,B-ORG
Director,I-ORG
&,I-ORG
Managing,L-ORG
partner,O
B.JAYA,B-PER
PRAKASH,L-PER
.,O
S,O
/,O
O.,O
B,O
JAGANNADHA,B-PER
RAO,L-PER
',',O
aged,O
about,O
33,O
years,O
.,O
Occ,O
Business,O
R,O
/,O
O,O
BHEL,O
-,O
LIG-6,O
',',O
Ramachandrapuram,U-PER
',',O
Medak,B-ORG
District,L-ORG
',',O
AP,U-ORG
HEREINAFTER,O
CALLED,O
THE,O
SECOND,O
PARTY,O
THE,O
“,O
TENANT,O
”,O
WHICH,O
TERM,O
SHALL,O
MEAN,O
AND,O
INCLUDE,O
ALL,O
HIS,O
/,O
HER,O
HEIRS,O
EXECUTORS,O
ADMINISTRATORS,O
LEGAL,O
REPRESENTATIVES,O
AND,O
ASSIGNEES,O
Contd,O
..,O
2,O
..,O
..,O
2,O
..,O
Whereas,O
the,O
second,O
party,O
was,O
in,O
search,O
of,O
a,O
suitable,O
accommodation,O
for,O
his,O
business,O
purpose,O
by,O
name,O
and,O
style,O
of,O
*,O
’,O
M,O
/,O
S.,O
JP,O
INTERIO,O
',',O
”,O
&,O
M,O
/,O
S.”SRI,B-PER
JAYAM,L-PER
HOUSING,O
&,O
CONSTRUCTIONS,O
”,O
M,O
/,O
S.SRI,O
JAYAM,O
HOUSING,O
&,O
CONSTRUCTIONS,O
Pvt,O
.,O
Ltd,U-LOC
.,O
and,O
being,O
satisfied,O
with,O
the,O
FLAT,B-MISC
NO,I-MISC
204,L-MISC
',',O
2nd,B-LOC
Floor,L-LOC
',',O
BR,U-LOC
'''s',O
Sharada,B-LOC
Hema,I-LOC
durga,I-LOC
Galaxy,L-LOC
',',O
Situated,B-LOC
Chandanagar,L-LOC
',',O
Hydearabad-500,U-MISC
050,O
',',O
Ranga,B-LOC
Reddy,I-LOC
District,L-LOC
',',O
Andhra,B-LOC
Pradesh,L-LOC
.,O
Whereas,O
the,O
first,O
party,O
got,O
the,O
Flat,B-MISC
No.204,L-MISC
',',O
llnd,O
Floor,U-LOC
',',O
BR,U-LOC
'''s',O
Sharada,B-LOC
Hema,I-LOC
Durga,I-LOC
Galaxy,L-LOC
',',O
Situated,B-LOC
Chandanagar,L-LOC
',',O
Hydearabad-500,U-MISC
050,O
',',O
Ranga,B-LOC
Reddy,I-LOC
District,L-LOC
',',O
Andhra,B-LOC
Pradesh,L-LOC
',',O
and,O
offered,O
to,O
let,O
out,O
on,O
Rent,U-MISC
the,O
said,O
Flat,B-MISC
NO.204,L-MISC
',',O
llnd,O
Floor,O
',',O
BR,B-LOC
Sharada,I-LOC
Hema,I-LOC
durga,I-LOC
Galaxy,L-LOC
',',O
situated,O
at,O
Chandanagar,U-LOC
',',O
Hyderabad-500,U-LOC
050,O
',',O
Ranga,B-LOC
Reddy,I-LOC
District,L-LOC
',',O
Andhra,B-LOC
Pradesh,L-LOC
',',O
to,O
the,O
second,O
party,O
for,O
his,O
business,O
Purpose,O
on,O
the,O
terms,O
and,O
conditions,O
agreed,O
upon,O
by,O
both,O
the,O
parties,O
as,O
mentioned,O
below,O
.,O
NOW,O
THE,O
AGREEMENT,O
WITHNESSESTH,O
AS,O
UNDER,O
This,O
tenancy,O
is,O
for,O
a,O
period,O
of,O
11,O
months,O
commencing,O
from,O
06th,O
day,O
of,O
April,O
2013,O
the,O
date,O
on,O
which,O
possession,O
of,O
the,O
said,O
flat,O
is,O
delivered,O
and,O
time,O
to,O
time,O
it,O
will,O
be,O
extended,O
the,O
tenancy,O
period,O
with,O
consent,O
of,O
both,O
parties,O
The,O
monthly,O
Flat,B-ORG
Rent,L-ORG
is,O
of,O
RS,U-MISC
.,O
'13,000/-',O
(,O
Rupees,O
Thirteen,O
Thousand,O
Only,O
),O
per,O
month,O
and,O
payable,O
within,O
the,O
10th,O
day,O
of,O
same,O
month,O
.,O
The,O
tenant,O
paid,O
an,O
amount,O
of,O
'Rs.36,000/-',O
(,O
Rupees,O
Thirty,O
Six,O
Thousand,O
Only,O
),O
by,O
the,O
way,O
of,O
cash,O
as,O
the,O
advance,O
which,O
will,O
not,O
carry,O
any,O
interest,O
and,O
is,O
refundable,O
at,O
the,O
time,O
of,O
vacating,O
the,O
said,O
Flat,U-MISC
.,O
The,O
tenant,O
shall,O
pay,O
the,O
electricity,O
charges,O
&,O
maintenance,O
charges,O
of,O
the,O
said,O
flat,O
regularly,O
without,O
any,O
dues,O
.,O
The,O
first,O
arty,O
desires,O
to,O
terminate,O
the,O
tenancy,O
for,O
any,O
reason,O
or,O
the,O
second,O
arty,O
desires,O
to,O
vacate,O
the,O
said,O
Flat,U-MISC
can,O
be,O
terminated,O
by,O
ONE,O
month,O
notice,O
on,O
either,O
side,O
.,O
The,O
sad,O
flat,O
will,O
be,O
used,O
only,O
for,O
Business,O
purpose,O
and,O
it,O
will,O
be,O
in,O
a,O
proper,O
Tenantable,B-ORG
Condition,L-ORG
.,O
The,O
said,O
Flat,O
shall,O
keep,O
the,O
premises,O
with,O
all,O
fixtures,O
Electrical,O
installations,O
etc,O
...,O
In,O
condition,O
as,O
it,O
is,O
let,O
subject,O
to,O
reasonable,O
wear,O
&,O
tear,O
.,O
That,O
the,O
tenant,O
herein,O
shall,O
not,O
store,O
any,O
dangerous,O
or,O
highly,O
inflammable,O
material,O
in,O
the,O
demised,O
premises,O
at,O
any,O
time,O
.,O
At,O
all,O
times,O
',',O
during,O
the,O
term,O
of,O
tenancy,O
to,O
keep,O
and,O
maintain,O
the,O
premises,O
clean,O
',',O
Tidy,O
',',O
Healthy,O
in,O
and,O
watertight,O
in,O
all,O
seasons,O
and,O
further,O
in,O
good,O
and,O
substantial,O
repair,O
reasonable,O
wear,O
&,O
tear,O
expected,O
.,O
The,O
terms,O
and,O
conditions,O
arrived,O
at,O
above,O
by,O
both,O
the,O
parties,O
are,O
with,O
their,O
own,O
free,O
will,O
and,O
consent,O
and,O
without,O
any,O
coercion,O
or,O
dues,O
from,O
anybody,O
.,O
WITNESSES,O
:,O
OWNER,O
l.,O
TENANT,U-PER
